muscatdaily.com 2012-05-18

# Privacy policy - Muscat Daily|Oman Newspaper

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you submit an inquiry or a complaint to us, you may be asked to provide your contact details (name, GSM number, e-mail id and mailing address).

When you submit your personally identifiable information through www.muscatdaily.com, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this privacy policy.

We will use the information you provide us only for the purpose of responding to your inquiry or in connection with the service for which you provided such information. We may forward your contact information and inquiry to other divisions of our company if we feel that they can best address your inquiry or provide you with the requested service.

We may also use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics or developing marketing plans.

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Such third parties may have access to the information needed to perform their functions, but are not allowed to use such information for any other purpose.

We may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, to the concerned regulatory body, government department or a court of law so as to comply with the applicable laws and regulations of the Sultanate of Oman.

If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.

For any questions or comments regarding our information or security practices, you may contact us by e-mail at _muscatdaily@apexmedia.co.om_  or by mail at: **The Editor, Muscat Daily, Apex Press and Publishing, PO Box 2616, Ruwi 112, Muscat, Sultanate of Oman.**
